{"Topic": "Population", "Subject": "General Knowledge", "Data": [{"Question": "What percentage of World\u2019s population lives in India?", "op1": "16.5%", "op2": "17.5%", "op3": "20%", "op4": "15%", "Answer": 3}, {"Question": "At the present rates of population growth of India and China, by which year is India likely to overtake China as the world\u2019s most populous country?", "op1": "2025", "op2": "2040", "op3": "2030", "op4": "2050", "Answer": 3}, {"Question": "During which decade did India see a negative population growth?", "op1": "1901-11", "op2": "1931-41", "op3": "1911-21", "op4": "1951-61", "Answer": 1}, {"Question": "Which among the following is the least populated state in India?", "op1": "Sikkim", "op2": "Goa", "op3": "Manipur", "op4": "Mizoram", "Answer": 4}, {"Question": "Which state in India has the lowest number of females in comparison to males?", "op1": "Bihar", "op2": "Rajasthan", "op3": "Punjab", "op4": "Haryana", "Answer": 2}, {"Question": "Which among the following countries has a better gender ratio than India?", "op1": "Bhutan", "op2": "Pakistan", "op3": "China", "op4": "Afghanistan", "Answer": 1}, {"Question": "What is the overall literacy rate of India as per 2011 census?", "op1": "74.04%", "op2": "82.14%", "op3": "76.06%", "op4": "65.5%", "Answer": 2}, {"Question": "Next to Delhi, which is the most populated Union Territory in India?", "op1": "Chandigarh", "op2": "Puducherry", "op3": "Daman and Diu", "op4": "Andaman and Nicobar", "Answer": 4}, {"Question": "Which of the following statements is/are true?", "op1": "1 only", "op2": "2 only", "op3": "Both 1 and 2", "op4": "Neither 1 nor 2", "Answer": 2}, {"Question": "Which of the following statements is/are true?", "op1": "1 only", "op2": "2 only", "op3": "Both 1 and 2", "op4": "Neither 1 nor 2", "Answer": 1}, {"Question": "Which of the following statements is/are true?", "op1": "1 only", "op2": "2 only", "op3": "Both 1 and 2", "op4": "Neither 1 nor 2", "Answer": 2}, {"Question": "Which of the following statements is/are true?", "op1": "1 and 2 only", "op2": "1 and 3 only", "op3": "2 and 3 only", "op4": "All the three", "Answer": 3}, {"Question": "Which of the following is being taken as the census moment since 2001?", "op1": "00.00 hrs of 01 Apr", "op2": "Sunrise of 01 Apr", "op3": "00.00 hrs of 01 Mar", "op4": "00.00 hrs of 31 Mar", "Answer": 2}]}